Lesson 43. Fully insured. Insurance companies are normally willing to ensure anything.
第43课。完全保险。保险公司通常愿意确保任何事情。
Ensuring public or private property is a standard practice in most countries in the world.
确保公共或私有财产是世界上大多数国家的标准实践。
If, however, you were holding an open-air garden party or a Fed it would be equally possible to ensure yourself.
但是，如果您举行了露天花园聚会或美联储，则同样有可能确保自己。
In the event of bad weather, needless to say, the bigger the risk an insurance company takes,
不用说，如果天气恶劣，保险公司承担的风险就越大
the higher the premium you will have to pay.
您必须支付的保费越高。
It is not uncommon to hear that a shipping company has made a claim for cost of salvaging a sunken.
听到一家航运公司已经索取了挽救沉没的成本的要求，并不少见。
Ship, but the claim made by a local authority to recover the cost of salvaging the sunken pie dish must.
船，但是地方当局提出的要求收回挽救沉没馅饼的费用。
Surely be unique. Admittedly it was an unusual pie dish.
肯定是独一无二的。诚然，这是一种不寻常的馅饼。
For it was 18 feet long and 6 feet wide.
因为它长18英尺，宽6英尺。
purchase: v.   买, annual: adj. 一年一度的
It had been purchased by a local authority so that an enormous pie could be baked for an annual fair.
它是由地方当局购买的，因此可以为年度博览会烘烤巨大的馅饼。
The pie committee decided that the best way to transport the dish would be by canal.
派委员会决定，运输这道菜的最佳方法是运河。
So they ensured it for the trip. Shortly after it was launched,
因此，他们确保了这次旅行。发射后不久
the pie committee went to a local inn to celebrate.
派委员会去了当地的旅馆庆祝。
teenager: n.  （13至19岁的）青少年
At the same time, a number of teenagers climbed onto the dish and held a little party of their own.
同时，许多青少年爬上了盘子，举办了自己的小聚会。
Dancing proved to be more than the dish could bear.
事实证明，跳舞超出了这道菜的含义。
capsize: v.   （船）翻
For during the party it capsized and sank in seven feet of water.
因为在聚会期间，它在七英尺的水中倾斜并沉没。
The pie committee telephoned a local garage owner who arrived in a recovery truck to salvage the
派委员会打电话给当地的车库老板，后者乘坐恢复卡车挽救了
shiver: v.   打颤，发抖
pie dish, shivering in their wet clothes.
馅饼盘，穿着湿衣服发抖。
teenager: n.  （13至19岁的）青少年, dive: v.   （头向下）跳水
The teenagers looked on while three men dived repeatedly into the water to locate the dish.
青少年看着，三名男子反复跳入水中以找到菜。
They had little difficulty in finding it,
他们找不到难以
haul: v.   拖曳
but hauling it out of the water proved to be a serious problem.
但是将其从水中拖出是一个严重的问题。
The sides of the dish were so smooth that it was almost impossible to attach
盘子的侧面是如此光滑，几乎不可能固定
rim: n.   （圆形物品的）外沿，边
hazards and chains to. The rim without damaging it.
危害和链条。边缘没有损坏它。
winch: n.   绞车
Eventually chains were fixed to one end of the dish and a powerful winch was put into operation.
最终，链条固定在盘子的一端，并进行了强大的绞车。
The dish rose to the surface and was gently drawn towards the canal bank.
这道菜升至表面，并轻轻地朝着运河堤。
agonizing: adj. 精神紧张的，提心吊胆的, perch: v.   处于（高处）, precariously: adv. 危险地，不稳固地
For one agonizing moment, the dish was perched precariously on the bank of the canal
在一个痛苦的时刻，这道菜被p不休地栖息在运河的河岸上
overbalance: v.   失去平衡
but it suddenly overbalanced and slid back into the water. The men were now obliged to try once more.
但是它突然过度平衡并滑入水中。这些人现在不得不再次尝试。
clamp: n.   夹钳，夹板
This time they fixed heavy metal clamps to both sides of the dish so that they could fasten the
这次他们将重金属夹在盘子的两侧都固定
vertically: adv. 垂直地
chains. The dish now had to be lifted vertically because one edge was resting against the
链。现在，这道菜必须垂直抬起，因为一个边缘在靠在
winch: n.   绞车
side of the canal. The winch was again put into operation and one of the men started up the truck.
运河的一侧。绞车再次投入运营，其中一名男子启动了卡车。
Several minutes later, the dish was again put into operation and one of the water.
几分钟后，这道菜再次投入运行，其中之一是水。
torrent: n.   激流，洪流
Water streamed in torrents over its sides with such force that it set up a huge wave in the canal.
水在其两侧的洪流中流动，以至于在运河中建立了巨大的波浪。
rebound: v.   弹回
There was danger that the wave would rebound off the other side of the bank and send the dish.
有危险的危险，波浪将反弹从银行的另一侧反弹，然后寄出盘子。
Plunging into the water again. By working at tremendous speed, the men managed to get the dish
再次坠入水中。通过以极大的速度工作，这些人设法得到了这道菜
on to dry land before the wave returned.
波浪返回之前，要进入干燥的土地。